♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
["Mr. Tailor" playing]
- ♪ Fix it ♪
- ♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
♪ Holding the scissors ♪
♪ One cut, and it's settled ♪
[security officer, in English]
Do you happen to know this person?
[Dmitri, in English] I have no other way
to contact him.
[in English] I'm very sorry, gentlemen,
but I couldn't help you.
[Samir, in English] You have a lover?
[in English] You give me a try
to make you feel real good.
PREVIOUSLY
You're vulgar!
Cathy?
[in English] Is that…
Karla?
Someone recognized me here,
and I need to avoid them.
Don't leave me. Karla, please.
[in English] …starts at one million pesos.
[in English] One point six million!
This cop seems to have a lot of money.
[in English] One point seven million.
[in English] 2,100,000 pesos.
[in English] Two point five million.
He can have it. It wouldn't fit me anyway.
I won't expose Atoy.
[Dmitri] He's still Janine's father.
[in English] It is best
you stay away from him.
[Karla] Needle on the move.
He received a text message
from someone with a letter B.
I'll take care of Needle.
- [grunts and groans]
- [thumps]
Your boyfriend is rich. Businessman?
No! Police.
Papa Kiko.
[Karla] Boyet is here,
carrying the suitcase.
[Emerson] Boss KM is Kiko Meneses,
not Kevin Martinez.
We're following the wrong needle.
[man] Let go of my boyfriend!
What's the matter with you?!
It's like you're not ready for my arrival.
Am I really your child?
[music fades]
You speak so harshly.
You just got scolded…
and now you're like that?
You're already sulking?
Well, that's what I feel.
- [sobbing]
- [melancholic music playing]
Well, you're wrong!
You know, the reason I do
all of that is because…
I want to make it up to you.
[Olga] I have many shortcomings
when it comes to you, right?
I-I want to give you a good life!
You saw it, Ibyang!
They almost riddled me with bullets!
Right? I tumbled and rolled there!
Because I want to make your life better!
I'll do everything for you!
I'm fine even if we're not rich, Mama.
[Ibyang] But if you're struggling
with your job,
there are other jobs.
[sighs]
This is the only thing I know how to do!
And now, I even have to hustle to pay
for all the damages you caused!
[somber music playing]
Now, you're saying
you're not my child? Huh?
You know, you?
You make me feel bad too.
[music fades]
But do I have time to sulk?
[epic music playing]
I'm sorry, Mama!
[sobbing]
[suave theme music playing]
[motorcycle revving]
[sewing machine whirring]
[scratches]
[snipping]
[clicking]
[sewing machine clacking]
- [gun cocks]
- [gunshots]
[gunshots]
[clicking]
[snipping]
[music swells]
[electronic blipping]
[muffled chattering in the distance]
[suspicious music playing]
Thread 1, can you hear me?
Scissors is carrying the button.
They're now checking in.
[Karla] I repeat. They're checking in.
Thread 1?
Mini Thread? Mini Thread.
[music fades]
[sneaky music playing]
- Karla.
- What, Gavin?
You're giving me a heart attack!
[in English] Heart attack or heartbreak?
Well, both are painful anyway.
I'm sorry.
I'm getting bored here.
Nothing exciting is happening.
What about inside? How is it?
A lot is happening.
Did you see those two men?
[Karla] There, they're the ones
we're chasing.
And that suitcase?
It contains five million pesos,
which we need to get.
[music swells]
- [thumps]
- [grunts]
[in English] Sorry, sorry.
Watch where you're going.
Be thankful I'm in a hurry.
[pensive music playing]
I bumped into that guy earlier.
He seems like a war freak.
I just avoided him.
That's why we need a strategy,
so we don't get into a fight.
How?
[music fades]
[in English] I have a bright idea.
[action music playing]
[music fades]
[clears throat] Uh, boss.
[suspicious music playing]
Boss, I just want to clarify something.
Uh…
We're just friends, okay.
You're crazy!
Of course we'll get a room,
and that's where we'll count the money.
Ah, because it's a couple…
And if there's something missing…
Boss, it's complete.
Remember our deal, boss, it's 10%.
- Okay, okay.
- [smirks]
[music fades]
You're shameless!
[action music playing]
[in English] Sweetheart!
Don't call me sweetheart!
Who are you meeting here?
I'm not meeting anyone.
Actually, this is a surprise for you.
[Gavin] I got a room
so we can have a staycation.
[Karla] Surprise? Where's your friend?
Didn't you say you're with your friend?
Sweetheart, you're the only one I love.
[Gavin] That's just my friend.
[Karla] You're really not honest, huh?
[Cathy, in English] Why would I care
about some couple that I don't even know?
[Karla] You're flirting with her, huh?
I'm not flirting with anyone else!
I'm not like that!
[Gavin] This is just a surprise for you!
That's why I got the room,
to surprise you.
[in English] That's Gavin!
[in English] That's my boyfriend, Mom!
We're having a staycation, right?
[in English] I'm sorry, sweetheart.
I don't want any conflict
between you and my best friend,
that's why sometimes I don't tell you.
[Karla] What if I make you choose, Gavin?
Who will you choose?
Your best friend or your girlfriend?
[tense music playing]
[Cathy, in English] Hey!
What's going on here?
Why are people saying you're a couple?
You told me you went with Jason
to Batangas.
[in English] Let me explain. Okay?
The thing I hate most is being deceived!
[in English] And you!
Is that why you're defending
Gavin so much,
because you're his side chick?
I'm not a side chick!
I'm not that kind of person, Cathy!
You're acting all innocent.
[in English] So, do you have feelings
for Gavin or not?
- Enough!
- [in English] Oh, you're defending her.
Let's talk outside.
No! I'm not going with you!
Oh! Wait.
You know, you're not funny anymore.
- You're causing trouble!
- [in English] Stop it!
[in English] That's my daughter!
You…
[squeals]
- You too!
- [shrieks]
- [gasps]
Let go of me!
[grunting]
Hey. Aren't you a cop?
[Karla] Stop them!
What are you doing?!
[Cathy's mom, in English] Call security!
Gavin! Stop them, oh!
[indistinct shout]
[Karla] Stop them! Gavin!
[Boyet] Let go of me!
[clamoring]
- [Karla] You're with him, right?
- [Cathy's mom, in English] Security!
What are you doing?
[Karla] You're so stupid, huh?
- [Boyet] I said let go of me!
- [clamoring]
I've been looking for you!
You know, I told you to go out, right?
Wait outside…
Sir, that's enough!
That's enough!
- Now, you're speechless?
- Is that it?
You know what? Whatever!
[in English] Gavin. Gavin, I'm sorry.
I'm okay now, Karla. Go.
[in English] So, Gavin, what?
Tell me the truth.
[in English] What's going on
between both of you?
Let's just talk outside. Please?
Fine.
[suspicious music playing]
Excuse me? That's my luggage!
What?
This is mine.
Here, look! The number on my stub.
[tense music playing]
[in English] That's mine!
Let's open this.
Let's go, let's go.
Emerson!
Where have you been? You took so long!
Well, you know, that lady there
asked me to make
a whole pitcher of iced tea.
Let's go. Let's go ahead.
She might catch me.
- Come on, come on.
- Yes, and Boyet might notice
that he has the wrong suitcase.
- Oh?
- Wait.
Where's Gavin?
He's with Cathy.
Cathy's here?!
It's a long story, brother. Later.
- Come on. I'll tell you later.
- [Paldo] Let's go.
- They might catch up to us here!
- Oh, hurry, hurry.
[in English] Sorry, sorry,
sorry, sorry, sorry.
[Emerson] The key, the key.
Where's my money?
[music fades]
Boss…
[tense music playing]
Boss, we have it!
You can't fool me, you animal.
You're trying to trick me?
You did this to get my money!
Where's the money?
No, boss.
If I was going to take your money,
- why would I meet you here?
- I'll kill you.
- I'll kill you, remember that.
- Boss, I do have the five million.
Hands up!
[music fades]
Both of you!
I'm a cop!
We'll take you to the station.
Explain yourselves there!
Why me?
Arrest him!
He's-- He's the one
who ordered me to steal!
No, both of you,
explain yourselves at the station!
[tense music playing]
[all] Yes!
- Five million pesos-pesos-pesos!
- Oh, wow!
At least now, we can return this
to the rightful owner.
Sis Ame is amazing!
Your idea of switching the suitcases
was brilliant.
- [Emerson] You're right.
- [Karla] Ah, you're awesome.
And Gavin's diversion idea
was also clever.
But Gavin got into trouble.
Boyet punched him,
and then he fought with Cathy.
Well, you didn't intend
for that to happen.
And besides, he insisted
on coming with us, right?
Even so. I allowed it, didn't I?
[gentle music playing]
Oh, oh, where are you going?
I'll look for Gavin.
I'll help him explain to Cathy.
That's the least I can do for him.
Karla will be okay.
First love really is different.
[in English] Gavin, you lied to me!
You told me you went
to Batangas with Jason!
[in English] And then, I find you here
with that… that girl?!
[in English] I'm sorry. Okay?
I just didn't want Karla
to become an issue,
so I didn't tell you she was with me.
- [in English] But we were just--
- [in English] Just what? Huh?
[in English] Acting like a couple
at a hotel?!
[in English] It's not like that.
[in English] Then what's it like, Gavin?
[in English] Gavin,
tell me exactly what's going on!
[somber music playing]
We were helping a friend.
[Gavin, in English] Okay? Karla and I…
We pretended to be a couple
fighting to help that friend.
That was our distraction tactic.
- Do you get it?
- What kind of distraction?!
What kind of help is that?
[Cathy, in English] Gavin,
I don't believe you!
Cathy.
- Karla.
- Wow!
You really came back! The audacity!
I came back because I don't want you
and Gavin to break up,
since I only asked him for help.
Our being a couple earlier
was totally just acting,
even the fight scene.
[gentle music playing]
Gavin is faithful to you,
and you have nothing
to worry about with me.
We're really just friends.
Would Gavin even look for someone else
if you're his girlfriend?
[in English] Okay, fine.
But this is the last time
this will happen.
[in English] Promise.
[music fades]
[in English] Hello, master!
[Atoy on phone, in English] Oh, hello?
How was your first mission?
[in English] Success, master!
- [in English] Success!
- [in English] Master!
You know, we got the package
without the target knowing?
- Isn't that great?
- [Emerson, in English] Mm, yes!
[in English] Very good. Proud of you.
[Ame on the phone, in English]
Oh, we really worked together, Atoy.
There was just a small hiccup at first,
but Karla and I quickly found a way
to switch the suitcase!
Karla?!
[tense music playing]
What-- [clears throat]
Uh, no, uh…
We really lacked manpower.
That's why we needed Karla.
You should have found someone else.
I told you.
I told you to never bring her along.
Something might happen to that girl.
Well, um…
You know Karla,
she's not "just-just", Atoy.
What do you mean "just-just"?
"Just-just", she's not ordinary.
No, no, no, she…
Oh, Atoy, she's like you.
Your sister is just as tough.
Mmm-mmm, mmm.
[mid-tempo rock music playing]
Sister?
[music fades]
Why? Are they siblings?
- [hushes]
- You're too loud.
Eh, ah… [clears throat]
Uh, yes, Atoy.
But the important thing is
we got the five million.
Our mission was successful.
Yes, Atoy.
[action music playing]
We thought this money
would never be returned to us.
Meneses and Boyet,
whom he ordered to steal,
are already in jail.
We also filed a case against them.
The construction of the school in Zambales
will finally begin in a month.
[Odette] Many children in remote areas
will benefit from that school.
We owe you so much. Thank you.
Oh, it's nothing.
We really just wanted to help.
You're amazing.
If we know anyone else who needs help,
- we'll refer them here.
- [Kurt] Hey. Oh, yes!
[in English] Spread the word!
The Children of the Thread
are here to stay!
[Ame] Oh my. [giggles]
- Spread the word, really?
- [Kurt] Hmm.
Sir, please accept this.
- [Emerson] Huh?
- Uh, it's just a small thing.
The staff pooled together for this.
It's less than 10,000 actually. Sorry.
Oh? No, it's not necessary.
You even went to the trouble, and…
This?
I can't… I can't have this.
I don't eat laing.
- Because I'm allergic.
- [both] Ah, laing!
[Emerson] Yes, no. And also, um…
I wish you hadn't gone to the trouble
because we really just wanted to help.
And it's also the first time
we've ever done this.
So, you have a free trial.
- [everyone chuckles]
- You're our first.
Please, accept it.
The amount you returned to us is so big,
for the children too.
It would be easier to accept
if it were cooked.
Oh, just kidding. Just kidding.
Just kidding, just kidding.
We'll go ahead now. Thank you very much.
- All right. We'll go ahead.
- [Emerson] Okay, okay.
- [Kurt] Take care.
- [Emerson] Take care. Take care, okay.
[in English] Bye-bye.
[sneaky music playing]
- Hey, it's like…
- Hmm.
- This feels good.
- It's amazing, right?
Those are good items.
Now I know how Atoy felt.
It really feels good to help, right?
Honestly, Boss E,
even if you didn't do much
in our first mission,
except make iced tea?
[Emerson] Wow!
- [giggles]
- No!
The Children of the Thread
wouldn't exist without you.
So, for the success
of Operation Suitcase!
- [all, in English] Cheers!
- [in English] Hey, cheers! Cheers, cheers!
[giggles]
- [lively chattering]
- [light music playing]
[crickets chirping in the distance]
[melancholic music playing]
[Dmitri, in English] Promise me, child.
You'll stay away from Atoy.
That's what I've been doing, Dad.
That's why Janine and I are leaving.
We're just waiting for her US visa.
[in English] It is best
you stay away from him.
Why does it feel like we're not moving?
Yes, I noticed too.
Well, because you're rowing that way.
I'm rowing this way.
- [Atoy] Well, I thought…
- We really won't move.
- Hello?
- Well, isn't that where we're going?
[chuckling]
[music fades]
[crickets chirping in the distance]
[phone ringing]
Audrey?
[gentle music playing]
Audrey, are you there?
The people at the Zahran embassy
are looking for you,
Samir and his men.
They have an AI-generated photo
of your face.
So, be careful.
Thank you for… for the warning.
Ah, and you, how are you?
[in English] This isn't
a social call, Atoy.
Let's not exchange pleasantries.
[in English] I have to go.
Audrey, wait.
[Atoy on the phone] Audrey…
I still love you.
[melancholic music playing]
You and Janine.
[Atoy on the phone] And, ah…
I know you still love me.
[Atoy] You even called me to warn me.
Thank you for--
[line beeping]
- Audrey?
- [line beeping]
[music fades]
[melancholic music playing]
[sobbing]
[in English] Please, please. Please.
[in English] Please, please.
[in English] Please.
[Ame on phone] There,
we recovered the suitcase!
The school construction
will now push through.
Our first mission was successful!
Yay.
Oh? Why are you sad?
Is it because
you weren't part of the mission?
Well, Tatoy forbade you, remember?
Because…
I really miss you and Tatoy, Sis Ame.
Hey, Ibyang, what happened?
Mama Olga scolded me.
Because I broke something.
And now she must pay
a huge amount to the owner.
[Ibyang on phone] I didn't
mean to, Sis Ame.
[sobs] I thought
she was in danger.
I thought I was saving her.
But…
I just added to her headache.
Ibyang, don't say that.
Of course, it's natural for your mom
to get angry with you,
because she's just human too.
She's led by emotions,
but she's also a mother.
She'll be angry now, nag you all day,
but tomorrow, everything will be fine.
Really, Sis Ame?
I'm just afraid she'll give me away
if she doesn't want me anymore.
Ibyang, she won't do that.
She searched for you
for a long time, didn't she?
Mama Olga loves you very much.
Just show her that
you're sorry. Make it up to her.
Then everything will be okay.
[sighs] Don't cry anymore, okay?
Olga, the child has only been
with you for a week,
and you're already asking
for next month's pay?
Well, I understand that, madam.
I was just hoping maybe
you could help me.
Maybe it could be included
in the miscellaneous fees?
[scoffs, in English]
It's your fault anyway.
You left her.
If you hadn't done that,
she wouldn't have followed you
to your workplace.
[sighs]
[in English] Just do your job well,
and I may consider giving you a bonus.
Well, there you go, madam.
That would be a big help.
Um, what are the plans for the child?
Don't concern yourself with that.
[suspicious music playing]
Sir, you're there.
Yes, I've been here.
I heard what you said to my wife.
Be thankful she didn't hang up on you.
Do what we agreed on.
That's your only job. Okay?
[line beeping]
[music fades]
"Do what we agreed on.
That's your only job."
[sighs]
So grumpy.
[pensive music playing]
[sneaky music playing]
[phone ringing]
Hello. Friend?
I thought of something
we could make money from.
It's big money.
[music swells]
[electronic blipping]
[tense music playing]
Don't be swayed
by his cuteness and smiles at you,
even if he's your friend.
[Cita] He's a Regalia.
And in the end,
he will still choose his family.
- [Red, in English] How's Janine?
- [Audrey] Still crying.
She said she suddenly remembered
the one who wanted to kidnap her.
[Audrey] Tell me.
Do you know the man
who wanted to take my daughter?
I was accused of being
an accomplice of that
female scammer.
[Olga] Ibyang?
Oh. Something like that.
She looks like her.
UP NEXT
What are you doing out here?
Come on. Get inside the car.
I won't go with you.
Why?
You're a liar!
It's impossible you're my mother.
You're a scammer!
♪ Holding the scissors ♪
♪ One cut, and it's settled ♪
♪ Fix it ♪
Subtitle translation by: Rachel C. Arias